Narrator: 1
Speaker: Have you ever tried to learn something new and failed?
Narrator: 2
Speaker: How important is it to know how to drive?
Narrator: 3
Speaker: How long do you usually spend deciding what to wear in the morning?
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Have you ever forgotten to turn off your phone during a class or concert?
Narrator: 5
Speaker: Where are you hoping to go for your next holiday?
Narrator: 6
Speaker: Are you planning to go anywhere next weekend?
Narrator: 7
Speaker: Would you like to work or study in another country?
Narrator: 8
Speaker: Have you ever pretended to be ill when you weren’t?
Narrator: 9
Speaker: Do you think it’s important to learn to cook at school?
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Do you think it’s possible to stay friends with an ex-boyfriend or girlfriend?